{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "$f(x) = \\ln(\\ln{x^{x^{2}}})$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt1",
      "answer": "3/e",
      "answer2": 1.103638,
      "prompt": "What is the $\\small \\textbf{instantaneous rate of change}$ of $\\small \\boldsymbol{f(x)}$ at $\\small \\boldsymbol{x = e}$",
      "extra": "Enter your answer symbolically",
      "solution": "$\\frac{3}{e}$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b1",
      "submission": "calc1t2s1",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "shortanswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\int_{0}^{1} \\sqrt{x+10} \\,dx$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt2",
      "answer": 10,
      "prompt": "Which of the following $\\small \\textbf{limits}$ would correctly correspond the following $\\small \\textbf{integral}$.",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$\\lim_{n\\rightarrow \\infty } (\\sum_{i=1}^{n}\\frac{1}{n}\\sqrt{\\frac{i}{n}+10})$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b2",
      "submission": "calc1t2b2",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "multiplechoice",
      "A": "$\\lim_{n\\rightarrow \\infty } (\\small \\displaystyle \\sum_{i=1}^{n}\\frac{1}{n}\\sqrt{\\frac{i}{n}+10})$",
      "B": "$\\lim_{n\\rightarrow \\infty } (\\small \\displaystyle \\sum_{i=1}^{n}\\frac{1}{n}\\sqrt{\\frac{i}{n}+5})$",
      "C": "$\\lim_{n\\rightarrow \\infty } (\\small \\displaystyle \\sum_{i=1}^{n} \\sqrt{\\frac{i}{n}}+10)$",
      "D": "$\\lim_{n\\rightarrow 0 } (\\small \\displaystyle \\sum_{i=1}^{n}\\frac{1}{n}\\sqrt{\\frac{i}{n}+10})$",
      "E": "$\\lim_{n\\rightarrow \\infty } (\\small \\displaystyle \\sum_{i=1}^{n}\\frac{1}{n}\\sqrt{\\frac{1}{n}+10})$"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\int_{0}^{\\frac{1}{2}} \\cosh{2x}\\,dx$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt3",
      "answer": "0.587601",
      "answer2": 0.587601,
      "prompt": "Use $\\small \\textbf{U-Substitution}$ to evaluate the following $\\small \\textbf{definite integral}$",
      "extra": "Enter your answer symbolically",
      "solution": "$\\frac{e^{2}-1}{4e}$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b3",
      "submission": "calc1t2s3",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "shortanswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\lim_{x\\rightarrow \\infty} (\\frac{e^{x}}{\\ln{x}})$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt4",
      "answer": 30,
      "prompt": "$\\small \\textbf{Evalute}$ the following $\\small \\textbf{limit}$",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$-\\infty$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b4",
      "submission": "calc1t2b4",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "multiplechoice",
      "A": "$0$",
      "B": "$1$",
      "C": "$-\\infty$",
      "D": "$\\infty$",
      "E": "$-1$"
    },
    {
      "question": "$f(x) = \\ln{3x} + \\tan{2^{x}}$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt5",
      "answer": 20,
      "prompt": "Determine $\\small \\boldsymbol{f'(x)}$",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$\\frac{1+\\sec^{2}({2^{x}})\\cdot2^{x}\\ln({2})x}{x}$   ",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b5",
      "submission": "calc1t2b5",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "multiplechoice",
      "A": "$\\frac{1+\\sec^{2}({2^{x}})\\cdot2^{x}\\ln({2})x}{x^{2}}$",
      "B": "$\\frac{1+\\sec^{2}({2^{x}})\\cdot2^{x}\\ln({2})x}{x}$",
      "C": "$\\frac{3+\\sec^{2}({2^{x}})\\cdot2^{x}\\ln({2})x}{x}$",
      "D": "$\\frac{-1+\\sec^{2}({2^{x}})\\cdot2^{x}\\ln({2})x}{x}$",
      "E": "$\\frac{1+\\sec^{2}({2^{x}})\\cdot2^{x}\\ln({2})}{x^2}$"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\begin{cases} x^{3} + 2x^{2} -5 & 0 \\leq x < 5 \\\\ \\frac{1}{x^{2}} & 5 \\leq x \\end{cases}$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt6",
      "answer": 50,
      "prompt": "At what point $(x,y)$ does the following $\\small \\textbf{piecewise function}$ have an $\\small \\textbf{absolute minimum}$?",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$(0,-5)$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b6",
      "submission": "calc1t2b6",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "multiplechoice",
      "A": "$(5,170)$",
      "B": "$(5,\\frac{1}{25})$",
      "C": "$(0,0)$",
      "D": "$(-5,0)$",
      "E": "$(0,-5)$"
    },
    {
      "question": "$f(x) = \\sinh({\\cosh{(\\ln{(\\ln{x})})}})$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt7",
      "answer": "1.601919",
      "answer2": 1.601919,
      "prompt": "$\\small \\textbf{Evalute}$ the following function at $\\small \\boldsymbol{x = e^{2}}$.",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$\\frac{-1+e^{\\frac{5}{2}}}{2e^{\\frac{5}{4}}}$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b7",
      "submission": "calc1t2b7",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "shortanswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt8",
      "answer": 40,
      "prompt": "Which of the following is $\\small \\textbf{false}$ regarding the satisfaction of the $\\small \\textbf{Mean Value Theorem}$?",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$\\footnotesize\\text{If f(a) = f(b) then there always lies a point on (a,b) such that f'(c) = 1}$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b8",
      "submission": "calc1t2b8",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "multiplechoice",
      "A": "$\\footnotesize \\text{f is continous on the interval [a,b]}$",
      "B": "$\\footnotesize \\text{f is differential on the interval (a,b)}$",
      "C": "$\\footnotesize \\text{There is a point c on (a,b) such that f(b) - f(a) = f'(c)(b-a)}$",
      "D": "$\\footnotesize\\text{If f(a) = f(b) then there always lies a point on (a,b) such that f'(c) = 1}$",
      "E": "$\\footnotesize \\text{There is a point c on (a,b) such that }\\frac{f(b)-f(a)}{f'(c)} = (-a+b)$"
    },
    {
      "question": "$f(x)=\\frac{x-4}{x^{2}-16x}$",
      "attempts": "calc1t2attempt9",
      "answer": 40,
      "prompt": "Find the $\\small \\textbf{intervals of increase}$ on $\\small \\boldsymbol{f(x)}$",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$None$",
      "buttonName": "calc1t2b9",
      "submission": "calc1t2b9",
      "css": "prettyLatex",
      "type": "multiplechoice",
      "A": "$x>16$",
      "B": "$\\left\\{\\begin{matrix} 16>x \\\\ 16<x<\\infty \\end{matrix}\\right.$",
      "C": "$\\left\\{\\begin{matrix}-\\infty<x<0\\\\0<x<16 \\\\ 16<x<\\infty \\end{matrix}\\right.$",
      "D": "$None$",
      "E": "$-\\infty < x < \\infty$"
    }
  ]
}
